Ricardo Montero

Personal info



First name: Ricardo
Last name: Montero
Date of birth: 17/05/1992

Web: https://rjtm.github.io

Nationality: Venezuelan
Phone number: 584141271146

Email address: rjtm1992@gmail.com

Profile

Hard working web developer looking forward to build amazing tools. With a past in programming contests, I have a passion for solving problems of every kind. Javascript, Sass and PHP are my go to languages but I have experience in many others. Open to learning new things everyday and improve myself in every way possible.

Bachelor in Computer Science from the Central University of Venezuela.

Work experience

HiKeener CTO and Founder

01/2016 - present

Leader of a small group of developers in charge of building a tool for photographers and media production groups that is going to change the way they organize and work.

In this position I'm developing multiple web apps and hybrid apps with bleeding edge technologies and making decisions every day that shape the future of the company and its products.

EXP Development

CTO

11/2016 - present

Head of the technology crew behind this Software Development company, right now focused in creating an app for a videogames event that's going to set new standards in the industry.

Developing hybrid and web apps to be used in large scale scenarios with top notch frameworks.

KnowHow Publicidad Caracas Venezuela **Senior Developer**

05/2010 - 06/2016

Working with small clients to give them the tools they need to grow their business. Mostly landing pages and small custom solutions for galleries, shopping carts and work

showcases.

Education

Universidad Central de Venezuela Caracas Venezuela

Computer Science

09/2009 - 07/2015

First of my class Bachelor in Computer Science with a passion in programming contests that took me to Toronto Canada in 2010 and Bangkok Thailand in 2011 to compete in the International Olympiad in Informatics representing my country Venezuela. Later I joined the training team that is in charge of teaching the new competitors for the next Olympiads in informatics.



Programming Languages and Tools

ReactJS •••• Redux •••00 ES6 •••• AngularJS 00000 Angular >= 2 •••• Git •••• NodeJS •••00 Responsive •••• Ionic Framework •••• Laravel Framework ••••

Languages

Spanish English Native Full